Guide to the Bernard F. Burgunder Collection of George Bernard Shaw, [ca. 1810]-1990.
Bernard F. Burgunder Collection of George Bernard Shaw, [ca. 1810]-1990.
- Series X. Photographs of Shaw and Others
  - Photographs of Others
    - A - F
      - Cornell, Katharine, 1893-1974, [1938]; 1 photo (Box 51, Folder 21)
        [n.p.] Cornell in costume; signed. Inscribed to Stella [Mrs. Patrick Campbell]
      - Culver, Douglas, 1949; 1 photo + negative + envelope + 1 leaf (Box 51, Folder 21.5)
        Ayot St. Lawrence; Photo of Culver, Shaw's bee-keeper, taken by GBS. With note from B.F. Burgunder.
      - Forbes-Robertson, Sir Johnston, 1853-1937, [1900]; 1 photo (Box 51, Folder 22)
        [London] Cabinet card, signed by Forbes-Robertson.
      - French scenes, 1907,1911; 2 photos (Box 51, Folder 23)
        [France] 2 photos taken by Shaw: 1 in 1907 of a sculpture in a french church; the second taken in 1911 of a Joan of Arc statue in Ballon d'Alsace.
    - G - M
      - "Graphic Shaw" Cornell University Library Exhibit, Oct., 1985; 53 photos + 53 photos + negatives (Box 52, Folder 1)
        Ithaca; Photographs of all on display in the Cornell University Olin Library. Included are preliminary prints and negatives.
      - Gillmore, Georgina "Judy" (Musters), [n.d.]; 2 photos + negative (Box 52, Folder 2)
        [n.p.] 2 copies of Judy, Shaw's first cousin. Married Mr. Musters
      - Gillmore, Georgina "Judy" (Musters), 1942; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 2.5)
        Ayot St. Lawrence; Judy, Shaw's first cousin. Taken by GBS.
      - Grey Friars Chapel, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 3)
        [Eastbridge?]
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 4)
        [n.p.] Scene from "Anatol" showing Granville-Barker, Lillah, McCarthy, and Sir Nigel Playfair as the characters.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 5)
        [n.p.] Granville-Barker in the role of cadet in war.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo + negative (Box 52, Folder 5.5)
        [n.p.] Granville-Barker photo taken by GBS.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo + negative (Box 52, Folder 5.6)
        [n.p.] Charlotte Shaw and Granville-Barker in the role of cadet in war.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 6)
        [n.p.] Scene from "Anatol" showing Granville-Barker and Sir Nigel Playfair as the characters.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [1891?]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 7)
        [n.p.] Granville-Barker around age 14.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, 1916; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 8)
        [n.p.]
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, May, 1953; 3 photos + 1 leaf (Box 52, Folder 9)
        London; 3 different photos of the Harley Granville-Barker bust at the London National Theatre. Made by Jacob Epstein.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [1912/15]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 10)
        Stansted Wrotham, Kent; Photo of Granville-Barker's house; interior.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 11)
        [London] Portrait photograph.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 12)
        [n.p.] Granville-Barker in costume.
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Granville-Barker, Harley, 1877-1946, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Gurley, Walter Bagnal, [n.d.]; 2 photos + 1 leaf (Box 52, Folder 15)
        [n.p.] 2 copies of Gurley. Note dated February 13, 1967 from Bernard F. Burgunder enclosed
      - Hamon, Augustin Frederic, 1862-1945, [1909/10?]; 1 photo + envelope (Box 52, Folder 16)
        [n.p.] Photograph of the home of Hamon, purchased with a loan from Shaw.
      - Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928. The Dynasts., [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 17)
        [n.p.] Scene from "The Dynasts", an epic drama of war with Napoleon; 15 member of the cast unidentified.
      - Higgs, Clara Rebecca and Harry Batchelor Higgs, [1949?]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 18)
        [n.p.] Photograph of gravestone for them. Erected in their memory by Shaw who they served at Ayot Saint Lawrence.
      - Irving, Sir Henry, 1838-1905, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 19)
        [n.p.] Photo of Irving in costume.
      - Irving, Sir Henry, 1838-1905, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 20)
        [n.p.] Postcard portrait photo of Irving.
      - Irving, Sir Henry, 1838-1905, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Jones, Henry Arthur, 1851-1929, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 21.4)
        [n.p.] Portrait photograph of Jones.
      - Kim, cairn terrier, [n.d.]; 1 photo + 2 leaves (Box 52, Folder 21.5)
        [Ayot St. Lawrence] Kim, Shaw's cairn terrier. Photo taken by Shaw; with 2 notes of information.
      - Levetus, Nora Charrington, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 22)
        [n.p.] Levetus portrait photo in costume.
      - Lockett, Alice M., 1858-1942, 1881; 3 photos + negative (Box 52, Folder 23)
        [n.p.] Small tin type photo with 2 copies of same, plus negative.
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, [1900?]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 24)
        [n.p.] McCarthy in costume as Mercia in "The Sign of the Cross".
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, Jun.2, 1906]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 24.5)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of McCarthy.
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, 1929; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 25)
        [n.p.] Photograph of McCarthy as Lady Macbeth.
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, [1906?]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 26)
        [n.p.] Photo of McCarthy about the time of her marriage to Granville-Barker.
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, Sept., 1914; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 27)
        London; Photo of Mc Carthy in role of Madame O'Kraska in "Tante".
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 28)
        London; Photo of Mc Carthy in role of Queen in "Hamlet"
      - McCarthy, Lillah, 1875-1960, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 29)
        London; Cabinet card portrait photo of Mc Carthy.
      - Morris, May, 1862-1938, [1890?]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 30)
        [n.p.] May Morris with guitar photo.
      - Murray, Alma, [1882]; 1 photo (Box 52, Folder 31)
        [n.p.] Alma Murray portrait in costume; signed.
    - N - Z; Scrapbook
      - Patch, Blanche, 1878-, Nov., 1940; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder .4)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of Blanche Patch at "Shaw's Corner" in Ayot St. Lawrence. Taken by G.B.S.
      - Patch, Blanche, 1878-, Dec., 1963; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder .5)
        [n.p.] Christmas card with photo of Patch and Shaw on front.
      - Patch, Henry, [n.d.]; 3 photos (Box 53, Folder 1)
        [Winchelsea] 3 postcard photos of the Winchelsea Church where Rev. Henry Patch (Blance Patch's father) was once Rector.
      - Patch, Noel J. S., Oct.13, 1917; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 2)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of Noel J. S. Patch grave site at New British Cemetery.
      - Russell, Annie, 1864-1936, [1905]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 3)
        New York; Printed photo of Annie Russell and unidentified little boy (son?)
      - Scholefield, R.S., photographer, Jul.26, 1926; 2 photos + negative + 1 leaf (Box 53, Folder 4)
        Dublin; 2 copies of photo taken by Scholefield of Shaw's birthplace. Published in the Daily News, July 26, 1926. Not with information by Bernard F. Burgunder.
      - Shakespeare, William. The Winter's Tale, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 5)
        [n.p.] Photo of unidentified actor in the ole of Autolycus in "The Winter's Tale"
      - Shakespeare, William. Twelfth Night., [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 6)
        [n.p.] Photo of the set of the Granville-Barker production of "Twelfth Night".
      - Shakespeare, William. A Midsummer Night's Dream., [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 7)
        [n.p.] Photo of a fairy in the Granville-Barker production of "A Midsummer Night's Dream".
      - Shaw, Charlotte Payne-Townshend, 1859-1953, [1908?]; 4 photos + 1 postcard + envelope + 1 leaf (Box 53, Folder 8)
        [Ayot St. Lawrence] 4 different poses of Charlotte taken by Shaw; postcard has Charlotte on verso with dates 1857-1843. A note from Bernard F. Burgunder says they came via Dan H. Laurence. Postcard forms part of the Ann Elder Jackson Collection.
      - Shaw, Lucinda Gurly, [pre-1913]; 1 photo + 1 leaf (Box 53, Folder 9)
        Park Village West; Photograph of Lucina Gurly Shaw, taken and printed by GBS, her son. With note from B.F. Burgunder.
      - Shaw, Lucy Carr, 1897; 2 photos + 1 negative + 1 leaf (Box 53, Folder 10)
        New York; 2 copies of Lucy Carr Shaw photo. She was GBS's sister.
      - Stanbrook Abbey, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 11)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of Stanbrook Abbey
      - Swaffer, Hannen, 1879-1962, 1950; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 12)
        [n.p.] Portrait photo taken by the Daily Herald.
      - Terriss, Ellaline, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 12.5)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of Terriss.
      - Terry, Dame Ellen, 1848-1928, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 13)
        [n.p.] Cabinet card photograph of Ellen Terry in costume, signed.
      - Terry, Dame Ellen, 1848-1928, [1906]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 13.5)
        [n.p.] Cabinet card photograph of Ellen Terry in costume as Lady Cecily in "Captain Brassbound's Conversion"
      - Terry, Dame Ellen, 1848-1928, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 14)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of Ellen Terry in costume.
      - Terry, Dame Ellen, 1848-1928, [1890?]; 2 photos (Box 53, Folder 15)
        London; 2 cabinet cards of Ellen Terry taken at same sitting.
      - Thames North Shore, 1945; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 16)
        Thames north shore photo.
      - Tree, Viola, 1885-1938, [1895?]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 17)
        [n.p.] Postcard photo of Viola Tree.
      - Tunney, Gene, 1897-1978, [1926?]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 18)
        [n.p.] Photo of Tunney in boxing ring; signed.
      - Unidentified houses, [n.d.]; 5 photos (Box 53, Folder 19)
        [n.p.] 2 photos of one house; 3 postcard photos of another
      - Unidentified man, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 53, Folder 20)
        [St. Leonards-on-Sea] Portrait of "Harry"
      - University of Guelph Library. Bernard Shaw Exhibit Catalogue, 1989; 36 photos + 1 item (Box 53, Folder 21)
        Guelph; 36 slides and one exhibit flyer on the exhibition of Shaw at Guelph.
      - Winchelsea photos, [n.d.]; 9 photos + envelope (Box 53, Folder 22)
        [Winchelsea] Commercially published photos of Winchelsea buildings in an envelope.
      - Winchelsea Church, 1936; 2 photos (Box 53, Folder 23)
        Winchelsea; 2 photos taken by Shaw of the Winchelsea Church.
      - Scrapbook containing photos of Beatrice Stella Campbell (Mrs. Patrick Campbell) and some family photos, n.d. (Box 123)
- Series XI. Photographs of Shaw's plays
  - A - C
    - Admirable Bashville, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Arts Theatre Club; 2 copies of same photo
    - Admirable Bashville, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Admirable Bashville, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Admirable Bashville, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Androcles and the Lion, 1913; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 5)
      Lillah McCarthy and Shaw during a rehearsal
    - Androcles and the Lion, Jul.18, 1934; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Regent's Park; Open Air Theatre production
    - Androcles and the Lion, [1913]; 1 photo + 1 postcard (Box 54, Folder 7)
      New York; 1 photo of set; 1 advertising postcard with Lillah McCarthy and Granville-Barker.
    - Androcles and the Lion, Jul.5, 1984; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 7.5)
      Niagra on the Lake; Shaw Festival production, July 5, 1984.
    - Androcles and the Lion, [1943]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Androcles and the Lion, [1943]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Androcles and the Lion, [1943]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Annajanska, [Jun., 1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Annajanska, [Jun., 1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - The Apple Cart, [1946]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - The Apple Cart, [1946]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Arms and the Man, 1894; 10 photos (Box 54, Folder 15)
      Avenue Theatre; Cabinet cards including Yorke Stephes, Alma Murray and Florence Farr. This is the first production of the play; photos are Shaw's own with his annotations from April 21 until July 7, 1894.
    - Arms and the Man, [1894]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 16)
      [Herald Square Theatre] Katherine Grey as "Louka"; 2 printed photos pasted on recto and verso of same card..
    - Arms and the Man, [1981]; 3 photos (Box 54, Folder 17)
      London; 1 photo of each of the three sets.
    - Arms and the Man, 1 item (Box 54, Folder 17.5)
      Argent Television; Publicity flyer for the London stage production adapted for television.
    - Augustus Does His Bit, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Augustus Does His Bit, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Back to Methuselah: In the Beginning, [1947]; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 20)
      Arts Theatre Club
    - Back to Methuselah: In the Beginning, [1947]; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Back to Methuselah: In the Beginning, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Back to Methuselah: In the Beginning, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Gospel of the Brothers Barnabas, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Gospel of the Brothers Barnabas, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 25)
      Arts Theatre Club; 2 copies of the same photo.
    - Back to Methuselah: The Thing Happens, [1947]; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Thing Happens, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Tragedy of an Elderly Gentleman, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Tragedy of an Elderly Gentleman, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Tragedy of an Elderly Gentleman, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Back to Methuselah: The Tragedy of an Elderly Gentleman, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Back to Methuselah: As Far As Thought Can Reach, [1947]; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Back to Methuselah: As Far As Thought Can Reach, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Back to Methuselah: As Far As Thought Can Reach, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Back to Methuselah: As Far As Thought Can Reach, [1947]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Candida, [1903]; 1 photo (Box 54, Folder 36)
      [n.p.] Production photo
    - Candida, [1981]; 4 photos (Box 54, Folder 37)
      Circle in the Square; 4 photos
    - Candida, Jul.1, 1983; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 37.5)
      Court House Theatre
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, [1906]; 5 photos (Box 54, Folder 38)
      Court Theatre; 4 postcard photos; 1 printed photo.
    - Caesar and Cleopatra, 1955; 1 photo + 1 leaf (Box 54, Folder 39)
      Prague; Sisi Ruzicka as Cleopatra; with letter dated May 27, 1975 from Ivan Ruzicka to Bernard Burgunder.
    - Caesar and Cleopatra, 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 40)
      [Paris?] Production photos
    - Caesar and Cleopatra, [1906/07?]; 2 photos (Box 54, Folder 41)
      [n.p.] Johnston Forbes-Robertson and Gertrude Elliott in the title roles.
    - Caesar and Cleopatra, [1006/07?]; 3 photos (Box 54, Folder 42)
      [n.p.] Forbes Robertson as "Caesar"
  - D - O
    - The Dark Lady of the Sonnets, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - The Dark Lady of the Sonnets, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - The Dark Lady of the Sonnets, Jul.8, 1988; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 2.5)
      Niagra on the Lake, Shaw Festival production.
    - Devil's Disciple, 1930; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 3)
      London, Savoy Theatre
    - Devil's Disciple, 1900; 3 photos (Box 55, Folder 4)
      On Tour; 2 copies of 1 photo (1 cabinet card); single photo of third. Forbes Robertson as "Richard Dudgeon".
    - Doctor's Dilemma, [1906?]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 5)
      London; Harley Granville-Barker
    - Doctor's Dilemma, [1958]; 1 photo + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 6)
      [n.p.] Photo plus note identifying it as the film version and the cast.
    - Don Juan in Hell, [1952?]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Don Juan in Hell, [1952?]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Don Juan in Hell, [1952?]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Fanny's First Play, [1944]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Fanny's First Play, [1944]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Fanny's First Play, [1944]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Fanny's First Play, [1944]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Fanny's First Play, [1944]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Fanny's First Play, [1944]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Fascinating Foundling, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Fascinating Foundling, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Geneva, 1938; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 18)
      London, Saville Theatre
    - Glimpse of Reality, 1951; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Glimpse of Reality, 1951; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Great Catherine, 1968; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 21)
      Hollywood; Warner Brothers-Seven Arts film production
    - Great Catherine, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Great Catherine, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Great Catherine, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Heartbreak House, Jul.29, 1950; 7 photos (Box 55, Folder 25)
      London; "Picture Post" 7 printed photos of the Arts Theatre production.
    - Heartbreak House, Feb.2, 1958; 4 photos (Box 55, Folder 26)
      [London] BBC television production
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; photo (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Heartbreak House, [July, 1950]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - How He Lied To Her Husband, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - The Inca of Perusalem, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - The Inca of Perusalem, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - The Inca of Perusalem, Jul.5, 1985; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 36.5)
      Niagra on the Lake; Shaw Festival 1985
    - John Bull's Other Island, Jun.30, 1911; 1 photo + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 37)
      10 Downing St.; Production photo plus note from B. F. Burgunder dated February 17th, 1966. He talks of other photos not in folder.
    - John Bull's Other Island, Jul.5, 1985; 3 photos (Box 55, Folder 38)
      Niagra on the Lake; Shaw Festival, 1985.
    - Major Barbara, 1958; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Major Barbara, [1956]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 40)
      [New York]
    - Man and Superman, [1947]; 3 photos (Box 55, Folder 41)
      [London] 3 publicity shots of Frances Rowe who played "Ann Whitefield"
    - Man and Superman, [1949?]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 42)
      Embassy Theatre
    - Man of Destiny, [1912]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 43)
      [Tokyo]
    - Man of Destiny, 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 44)
      Arts Theatre Club; 2 copies of the same photo
    - Man of Destiny, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Misalliance, [1956]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 46)
      Hammersmith, Lyric Theatre; Printed photo.
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1902; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 47)
      [London] Printed photo of Shaw and Fanny Brough at rehearsal.
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, ]1902?]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 48)
      [London?] Fanny Brough as "Mrs. Warren"
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, [1951]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - The Music-Cure, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - The Music-Cure, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 53)
    - O'Flaherty, V.C., [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - O'Flaherty, V.C., [1951]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - O'Flaherty, V.C., [1951]; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - O'Flaherty, V.C., Jul.1, 1983; 1 photo (Box 55, Folder 55.5)
      Niagra on the Lake; Shaw Festival 1983
    - O'Flaherty, V.C., [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - O'Flaherty, V.C., [1951]; 1 photos (Box 55, Folder 57)
    - Overruled, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 58)
    - Overruled, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 59)
    - Overruled, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - P - Z
    - Passion, Poison, and Petrification, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Passion, Poison, and Petrification, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - The Philanderer, [1944]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - The Philanderer, [1944]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - The Philanderer, [1944]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Press Cuttings, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Press Cuttings, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Press Cuttings, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Press Cuttings, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Press Cuttings, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Pygmalion, 1914; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 11)
      His Majesty's Theatre; Mrs. Patrick Campbell as "Eliza Doolittle"
    - Pygmalion, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 12)
      [n.p.] 3 photos of film version of Pygmalion.
    - Pygmalion, 1914; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 13)
      His Majesty's Theatre; Roy Byford in role of "Bystander"
    - Pygmalion, 1944; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 14)
      Hammersmith, Lyric Theatre; Ellen Pollock as "Eliza Doolittle"
    - Pygmalion, 1935; 4 photos + 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 15)
      Berlin; "Film-Kurier" supplement, film brochure for the German production. A note describes it.
    - Pygmalion, 1978; 8 photos (Box 56, Folder 16)
      London; Play production photos.
    - Saint Joan, [1956]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Saint Joan, 1957; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 18)
      [n.p.] Film production
    - Saint Joan, [1970?]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 19)
      Circle in the Square; Lynn Redgrave as "Saint Joan"
    - Saint Joan, [1975]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 20)
      Toronto; Stratford Festival
    - Saint Joan, [n.d.]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 20.1)
      [London?] Sybil Thorndike as Joan. One is inscribed by her.
    - Shakes Versus Shav, [n.d.]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 21)
      [n.p.] Printed photo.
    - Shakes Versus Shav, [Aug., 1949]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 22)
      Malvern; Lanchaster Marionette Theatre; printed photo
    - Shakes Versus Shav, 1989; 1 photos (Box 56, Folder 23)
      Niagra on the Lake; Shaw Festival
    - The Shewing-Up of Blanco Posnet, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - The Shewing-Up of Blanco Posnet, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - The Shewing-Up of Blanco Posnet, [1951]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 1 photo (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, Jun.30, 1983; 3 photos (Box 56, Folder 30.5)
      Niagra on the Lake, Shaw Festival, Court House Theatre, 1983
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - The Simpleton of the Unexpected Isles, [1945]; 2 photos (Box 56, Folder 35)